(Arthur:)I can't catch a break today.
(Penny:)We'll pack up your stuff,
meet you at the hospital.
(Leonard:)Sorry things turned out this way.
Well, at this point, I'm just glad
someone's carrying me down the stairs.
(Sheldon:)Met my childhood hero,
now I get to ride in an ambulance.
(Sheldon:)Boy, if we can get him to do that calendar,
this will be the best day ever.
I can't believe we lost her.
(Bernadette:)What was I thinking? I'd be a terrible mom.
(Howard:)Maybe with the first one.
(Howard:)But kids are like pancakes,
the first one's always a throwaway.
(Howard:)- How's this look?
- It's fine.
(Bernadette:)- Where'd you get that picture of her?
- It's not her. I Googled "foo-foo little dogs."
(Howard:)It's Raj. Stay quiet.
Hey, heh, bad timing. Bernadette just took
Cinnamon out for a walk.